Scientists are concerned
as green areas are increasing.
Nature is warning us
that the world is heading for a crisis.
Global temperatures have peaked
for another year.
Species have died out,
millions of fish have died
due to bacteria from melting polar ice,
and the extent of this damage
is hard to predict.
The whole world is facing
its greatest crisis in history.
It's predicted that this crisis
will go on for several decades
or remain unresolved forever.
Many countries face food shortages.
People are starting riots.
Could this be the end of humanity?
This is a government announcement.
While people around the world still face
food shortages due to climate change,
our nation of Siam
remains abundant with resources
after being disconnected
from the outside world for over ten years.
Because of the Thai people's
unity and cooperation,
our nation is strong
and still stands today.
Send it out quickly or it'll spoil.
Close the doors.
We, the government,
pledge to restore the nation of Siam
to the civilization it once was.
Let us all take pride in our nation.
We'd like to thank you, citizens,
for your continued trust in us.
And we will continue to protect you.
Hey, Singh.
You're really quitting this job?
Yes.
Have you found my replacement?
What the fuck will you do next?
Go back to that underground boxing place?
Rin wants to move back to Chiang Dao.
No matter where you are,
it's all the same struggle.
INSECT FARMING PROJECT FOR FOOD SECURITY
THE FOOD OF TOMORROW,
NOURISHING ALL LIVES WITH HEART
You fucker!
Fuck. This batch will make me rich.
ZIAM
BANGKOK IN CHAOS AS MAJOR RIOT ERUPTS
AUTHORITIES ON HIGH ALERT!
PERMANENTLY CLOSED
BOXING STADIUM
Hey! How much water do you need?
Wait! It's for a lot of people!
- You want water or what?
- Yes, please.
Are you cutting in?
Hey! Run!
Many people are now gathering
to cause civil unrest.
This is irresponsible behavior.
Anyone who helps these people
is an offender
in the eyes of the government
and will face serious consequences.
MONDAY: I'M GOING OUT
FRIDAY: I'M WORKING THE NIGHT SHIFT
The crate broke.
Sorry, boss.
Just take this crate.
Singh.
Shit! He fucking cut my pay.
Fuck. He threw the cash in my face too.
There. That's yours.
Fuck this.
Here. As promised.
Shit!
Singh, it's fish.
We risked our lives for this?
We haven't had good food in ten years.
I'll get a knife. We'll split it.
Everyone, thank you for coming.
As Mr. Vasu is busy,
he asked me to step in
and meet you all today.
As we all know,
Mr. Vasu created this miracle
that helped all Thai people survive
a major food shortage.
But it was just the beginning.
Real change will begin now.
While the whole world
regresses into the past
and humanity sinks back to rock bottom,
Mr. Vasu has once again
made the impossible possible.
These fish are safe.
They're actually the best quality goods
Mr. Vasu got for his wife.
What are we waiting for?
Enjoy your meal.
Give it to me!
Mr. Vasu invites you all
to build a new food business with him.
And we'll become the world's food hub.
Think you're tough?
Hey!
What's happening?
Hey! Get out of here!
Are you done yet?
Where were you for so many days?
At work, of course.
You know it's dangerous.
Why do you keep doing it?
It's not that bad.
Sit down.
Does it have to get worse
before you wake up and smell the roses?
This is the last time, Rin.
You always say that, Singh.
I don't want to be left heartbroken…
If something happens to you.
Think about how I feel.
Sorry.
Forget it. You'll just do it again.
Rin.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Okay. I'm going to work now.
Wait, Rin.
Hurry home, okay?
Okay.
The current time is 8:00 p.m.
We are shutting down the electricity.
The government thanks all the citizens
for helping our nation save electricity.
Thank you.
Rin.
I've finished this book.
Great job.
I thought it was really easy.
Got any harder ones?
Did you argue with Singh again?
You look so sulky.
What was it about?
The same old thing, Mink.
He probably has his reasons.
Who would want to get hurt for no reason?
I'm scared he'll get himself killed.
I get it.
Right now,
there aren't many choices.
It's okay. I'm always ready
to protect you.
Protect yourself first. Look, I told you
to hang it around your neck.
I'm a big boy now, Mom.
Yeah, sure. Such a big boy.
During this crisis,
our hospital is ready
to take care of all citizens.
We also have additional support
from VS Corporation.
Please…
- How's the case from yesterday?
- Excuse me. Make way.
- Thank you.
- Please make way.
Hey, Mink.
Hey, Rin.
- I'll be upstairs.
- Okay.
I'll be the doctor's assistant.
- Don't bother Rin too much, okay?
- Okay, Mom.
Please make way.
- Careful, Buddy.
- Make way.
- Evening, Doctor.
- Evening.
You're much better.
You're free to go home.
Thank you very much, Doctor.
- We can discharge the patient in bed six.
- Yes, Doctor.
If you're feeling better, you can go home.
Great job, Doctor.
But my dad is in so much pain!
Please wait a moment.
I need to get the meds today!
Dr. Rin, it's time for the surgery.
All right. Buddy?
- Yes?
- I'm going up to the OR now.
Okay.
- Everything's ready inside.
- I'll be right there.
Dr. Rin? Come with me to the tenth floor.
I'm needed in surgery now, Director.
I'll get someone to take care of it.
Director, this is
a very high-risk patient. If...
The hospital is also at risk
if you don't come with me now.
Dr. Rin, you know how important
Mr. Vasu is to our hospital, don't you?
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Good evening, Director, Dr. Rin.
- Good evening, Director.
- Good evening.
Excuse me! Please make way!
Good evening, Mr. Vasu.
Nurse, suction, please.
Sir!
I'd like to ask you both
for advice on something.
I believe fish liver
could improve my wife's condition.
Start CPR now.
Charge to 200 joules. Clear.
Sir. Hold him down. Sir!
But Mr. Vasu, we're still not sure
if these fish will actually
benefit our patients.
My food has kept the entire nation alive.
Call the doctor.
Do you think I'd give my wife
something harmful?
Mr. Purich!
- Get out of the way!
- Mr. Purich!
So,
let me try it my way.
Just this once.
Or should I keep watching my wife
get blood transfusions?
It's very impressive
that Mr. Vasu found the fish.
But Director, we still don't know
if those fish are safe for our patients.
His company must have checked them.
You know how much
he wants his wife to recover.
What? What's going on?
What's going on?
Security, check it out!
We have an emergency
at Prachamit Hospital.
Unless it's absolutely necessary,
do not enter the area.
I repeat, we have an emergency
at Prachamit Hospital.
OUR DREAM HAS COME TRUE
…do not enter the area.
Currently, the Special Operations Force
is handling the situation.
Everyone, please remain calm.
Unless it's absolutely necessary,
do not enter the hospital area.
All these troops for just one madman?
…the Special Operations Force
is handling the situation.
- Excuse me.
- This way, please.
Right this way, please.
This way, please.
We can't confirm that.
- What's going on?
- We don't know that for sure yet.
- May I go in there?
- No, you can't.
- Please stay here.
- Please, I beg you.
- Please let me in. My husband's inside.
- We really can't do that.
We don't know what's going on either.
Please, I beg you. Just let me in.
- We can't.
- My husband…
- Hey, was that a man?
- That's so scary!
Is he dead?
SOF
Doctor?
Everyone, go back inside the building.
Those who disobey
will face serious consequences.
I repeat, those who disobey
I said back off!
Go back inside!
Don't come out, or we'll shoot!
- What's going on?
- Ma'am, easy. Easy, everyone.
Easy, everyone.
- Easy.
- What do we do?
- Is it bad?
- Just sit down.
Go. Stay calm.
Grandma.
Take Grandma over there.
Everyone, stay calm.
Calm down!
Slow down!
Hey, calm down!
What's going on?
Help!
Easy!
Move aside!
I'll be right back.
- Dr. Rin.
- Yes?
Don't leave me here.
All right.
Rin!
Where are you?
Rin, where are you?
Rin!
Singh.
Singh!
Singh, can you hear me? Singh.
Rin, where are you?
Rin.
Rin, where are you? Rin!
Whoa!
Somebody, help!
Help! Somebody! Anybody!
Stay away from me!
Don't you dare come any closer!
Let me go!
Get away from me!
Go away! Get away from me!
Hit it in the head!
Just hit it!
The brain controls everything!
Yeah! Just like that!
Whoa, that was damn cool.
I don't think I'm gonna make it!
You should run!
Tell my mom I love her very much!
Hey, wait for me! My mom works
on the third floor. Please take me there.
You know Dr. Rin?
We're best friends!
If we find my mom, we'll find Dr. Rin.
Tell me the way.
Damn, what a show-off.
Mom, where are you?
Mommy?
Mom.
- Has anyone seen my mom?
- Hey, kid.
Mom.
Where are you, Mom?
Mommy?
Go back inside the building now!
I repeat, go back inside the building now!
Don't shoot!
What's really going on, Doc?
- What's wrong with those people?
- We don't have any intel yet.
We can't conclude what's wrong.
Even public health officials don't know,
so who the hell will?
Should we have all the fuckers shot
and be done with it?
And how will you know who's who?
Send the doctors in too
so the strike team will know who's who.
And who are we sending in? Your squad?
I wouldn't want to send my team to die.
What's the total population of Bangkok?
Well,
around five million.
How many are in the hospital?
About 500.
Blow up the hospital.
Wait, what?
If we let them get out,
it won't just infect people in Bangkok.
It'll spread across the whole country.
We must be realistic.
Blowing up the hospital is the only way
we can solve this crisis.
We must do it for the majority.
Feeling better?
- Not too bad.
- It'll stop hurting.
It's okay. You're okay, right?
You're okay, right?
This is my mom's office.
Hey. Mom and Rin are on the fifth floor.
DR. RINLADA, PEDIATRIC SURGERY
FIFTH FLOOR, 10:00 P.M.
This way!
Go!
What are you doing?
Everyone will die anyway.
There's no escape now.
I love you, Dad.
Hey!
Hey, wait for me!
Go away!
Get away from me!
Help me!
I can't hold on anymore! Help me!
TRUE SOVEREIGNTY ARISES
FROM THE BREATH OF THE PEOPLE
TRUST IN US, THE SPECIAL GOVERNING COUNCIL
Mom!
Buddy!
I'm so glad you're okay.
I'm totally chill, Mom.
They can't hurt me.
Didn't I tell you to keep this close?
Dr. Rin's on the tenth floor.
How do you know me?
Dr. Rin talks about you every day.
Let's go find Rin together, Mom.
You go ahead with him.
I need to watch over the babies here.
Then I'll stay with you.
Please take care of him.
Come on. Let's go.
- Go where?
- Let's go now.
Let me go! I'm staying with Mom!
Buddy, listen to me.
You have to be strong.
Go with him.
Go with him!
- Come on.
- Let go!
- I'm staying with Mom!
Let go!
Let go, damn it! I'm staying with Mom!
Let me go! I'm staying with Mom!
Come on, let go of me! Let go!
Mom!
- Buddy, we gotta go.
- No, I'm staying!
Let me go!
Buddy! She's not your mom anymore.
No! I'm staying here! No! Let go of me!
Let go! Let go of me!
Mom!
Mom.
Mr. Vasu!
Can you open the door?
Mr. Vasu, please open the door for me.
Please, Mr. Vasu. Please open the door.
Mr. Vasu, please open the door for me!
I'm begging you. Please open the door!
Doctor.
You're not hurt?
No, I'm okay.
Take a seat.
Try to relax.
Relax, Doctor.
You're safe in this room.
All right.
What should we do next? We…
Don't worry.
We don't have to do anything.
Someone's coming to help us soon.
Don't worry.
TRUST IN US, THE SPECIAL GOVERNING COUNCIL
Sir, we have orders
to extract Mr. Vasu from the building.
Colonel.
Assemble your best squad
and get Mr. Vasu and his wife out.
That'd just be a suicide mission, sir.
This is an order.
Let's go. We should go on.
You go ahead.
I'll only hold you back if I come too.
Hey.
Your mom told you to be strong.
Then I'll be strong for Mom.
Let's go.
We'll get out of here soon, honey.
Isn't it ironic, Doctor?
I saved the whole country
when the disaster struck.
But now…
I can't even do anything
to help my own wife.
You've done your best for her.
These past five years,
you've always been by her side.
I think she knows it.
Doctor.
Yes?
Can you please get some blood for my wife?
I beg you, Doctor.
Can you please help my wife?
And I'll get you out of here.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
What will you do if you make it out?
Rin wants to move back up-country.
I'll take her there.
Rin's so lucky she has someone
who loves her this much.
Come with us.
Back away.
Hey, someone's here to help us!
We have 30 minutes.
Get Mr. Vasu and his wife out ASAP.
I repeat, we have 30 minutes.
Central command,
Alpha Team's heading to the tenth floor.
Let's go.
Hey!
Buddy, get to the door!
Medic, get the blood
for Mr. Vasu's wife stat
and take them to safety ASAP.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir!
Singh!
Rin!
Singh.
Hey! It won't open!
Buddy, move!
Get inside!
Singh!
Singh.
That's enough.
Central command.
We've lost our medic.
We need to bring the doctor.
Singh, they're here to help us.
Let's go, Buddy.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
Singh!
We've found the doctor!
Singh.
- Come on, Doc.
- Alpha reporting in.
- All targets secured.
- Doc, come on.
No!
- Let go!
- Heading to the rooftop.
Singh, don't fall asleep. Singh. Let go!
Singh!
Boss, there's a kid!
- Let go!
- Come on.
Singh!
Wake up! Singh! Wake up, Singh!
Hey!
- Singh!
- Can you hear me?
Singh!
Singh, watch out!
Rin, hide!
Singh.
Hold on, Singh.
Singh!
Singh.
Rin.
- We should run.
- Singh.
You need to rest.
I'm fine.
Can you just stop saying you're fine?
Rin.
Rin, I'm sorry.
Sorry I make you worry all the time.
I'm sorry too.
I'm just worried about you.
If anything bad happened to you…
I wouldn't know what to do.
Have some rest.
Rin.
What are you doing?
When we get out of here…
let's move back to Chiang Dao.
Singh, we're in trouble!
Let's go.
Buddy.
Rin!
Ann!
Mr. Vasu, we need to go now.
My wife's awake now.
- Mr. Vasu!
- Rin.
- Ann.
- We should go.
I love you.
I love you very much.
This way.
- Hurry.
- Let's go.
Run!
- Buddy!
- Rin!
Rin, you go ahead.
Singh! No!
Go! I'll catch up!
You'd better hurry!
Stop!
Are you hurt, Doc?
I'm not hurt.
Turn around!
Turn back around slowly.
Alpha, over.
Alpha, please report back. Over.
Where's Mr. Vasu's rescue team?
Come on, we need to evacuate.
There's one more coming up.
Please wait for him.
He'll make it.
No, there's no time.
- Wait a bit.
- He's right behind us. Please wait.
Wait just a tiny bit!
He saved us.
I'm begging you. Please wait for him.
I'm begging you.
Five more minutes.
Go. Wait in the chopper.
Go to the chopper!
Go! Move!
Come on, kid.
Watch your head.
Breathe deeply.
Doc, we gotta go!
- Wait. Not yet.
- Time's up!
Not yet. Wait.
Please wait! Don't take off!
Don't take off yet!
- Let go of it!
- Please, not yet!
Hey!
I beg you, don't take off yet!
Singh!
- Singh!
No! Please wait!
Singh!
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit